Vera Liu

Front-end engineer



About Me

I have been working in CommonWealth Magazine Group as a front-end engineer for five years.

I am a person who is positive, optimistic, outgoing and who has the courage to take any challenges.

Currently, I am learning web3-related knowledge and hope to apply it in conjunction with my existing knowledge in the future.

Education

(2011-2015)

FU JEN UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Chemistry

(2017-2018)

INSTITUTE FOR INFORMATION INDUSTRY, III

Training class for Web/APP front-end engineers

Contact

- veraaaaaliuuuuu@gmail.com
- https://github.com/veraaaaliu
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/yiling-liu-vera/

Skills

- vue (vue2/vue3/nuxt2/nuxt3)
- svelte (svelteKit)
- firebase
- qit
- figma

Experiences

(2018 - present)

CommonWealth Magazine Group

FRONT-END ENGINEER 4Y+

- Develop and Maintain company website.
 - o <u>smiletaiwan-lesson-plan</u>
 - o TRIPs
- · Landing pages.
 - sdgs / sdgs-podcast
 - o <u>futureMindset</u>
 - taipower
 - o smiletaiwan-sustainability
 - o <u>smiletaiwan-20anniversary</u>
- Develop tools to Increase work efficiency.
- Design-system.

(2020 - present)

FREELANCE DEVELOPER 2Y+

- Hospital dashboard.
- · School official website.
- Reservation system + Line liff pages.
- · Accounting system.
- · Landing pages.

